Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 5: Boxes 89-101
Archives Information File, Section 5: Boxes 89-101
- Box: 90, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 90, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Economic Opportunity Act, 1965; Publication (Box 90, Folder 21)
    Notes: December 1, 1965
  - Item 2: Summary of the Economic Opportunity Amendments of 1966, 1967; Publication (Box 90, Folder 21)
    Author: U.S. Office of Economic Opportunity
    Notes: January 1967
  - Item 3: Economic Opportunity Amendments of 1966, Publication (Box 90, Folder 21)
    Notes: September 29, 1966
  - Item 4: Public Law 89-794, 1966; Publication (Box 90, Folder 21)
    Notes: November 8, 1966
  - Item 5: Economic Opportunity Act, 1970; Publication (Box 90, Folder 21)
    Author: U.S. Committee on Labor and Public Welfare
    Notes: April 1970
  - Item 6: Economic Opportunity Act, 1964; Publication (Box 90, Folder 21)
    Notes: August 20, 1964
  - Item 7: Economic Opportunity Amendments, 1965; Publication (Box 90, Folder 21)
    Notes: September 14, 1965
- Box: 90, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 90, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Emergency Employment Assistance Appropriation, 1972; Publication (Box 90, Folder 22)
- Box: 90, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 90, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Employment Act, 1966; Publication (Box 90, Folder 23)
    Notes: February 1966
- Box: 90, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 90, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Interprative Bulletin of the Wage and Hour Administrator, 1964; Publication (Box 90, Folder 24)
    Author: Bureau of National Affairs
    Notes: April 24, 1964
  - Item 2: Interpretative Bulletin of the Wage and Hour Administrator, 1964; Publication (Box 90, Folder 24)
    Notes: May 1, 1964
  - Item 3: Guide to Equal Pay Act, Publication (Box 90, Folder 24)
  - Item 4: Equal Pay Act, 1963; Publication (Box 90, Folder 24)
- Box: 90, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 90, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Amending Sections 7 and 11 of the Clayton Act, 1949; Publication (Box 90, Folder 25)
    Notes: May 18, 1949
- Box: 90, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 90, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Guidelines for Evaluation of Employment Practices, 1974; Publication (Box 90, Folder 26)
    Notes: July 1974
- Box: 90, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 90, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Reporting and Disclosure Employee Retirement Income Security Act, 1975; Publication (Box 90, Folder 27)
  - Item 2: Coverage Under the Employee Retirement Income Security Act, 1975; Publication (Box 90, Folder 27)
  - Item 3: Fiduciary Standards Employee Retirement Income Security Act, 1974; Publication (Box 90, Folder 27)
- Box: 90, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 90, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Handy Reference Guide to the Fair Labor Standards Act, 1974; Publication (Box 90, Folder 28)
    Notes: May 1, 1974
  - Item 2: Wage and Hour Legislation in Action, 1938; Publication (Box 90, Folder 28)
    Author: National Consumers' League
    Notes: December 9, 1938
- Box: 90, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 90, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Application of the Fair Labor Standards Act to Employees Employed as Seamen, 1962; Publication (Box 90, Folder 29)
  - Item 2: Authorization of Established Basic Rates for Computing Overtime Pay, 1964; Publication (Box 90, Folder 29)
    Notes: February 1964
  - Item 3: Annulment of Withdrawal of Certificates for the Employment of Student Learners, Apprentices, Learners, Messengers, Handicapped Persons, Student Workers, and Full-Time Students in Retail, Publication (Box 90, Folder 29)
  - Item 4: Coverage of the Wage and Hours Provisions, Publication (Box 90, Folder 29)
  - Item 5: Coverage of the Wage and Hours Provisions: Part B, Publication (Box 90, Folder 29)
  - Item 6: Definition of Area of Production, Publication (Box 90, Folder 29)
  - Item 7: Determinations Under and Interpretations of Section 3(m) of the Fair Labor Standards Act, Publication (Box 90, Folder 29)
  - Item 8: Determinations Under and Interpretations of Section 3(m) of the Fair Labor Standards Act, Publication (Box 90, Folder 29)
  - Item 9: Interpretations, Publication (Box 90, Folder 29)
  - Item 10: Defining the Terms, Publication (Box 90, Folder 29)
  - Item 11: Defining the Terms, Publication (Box 90, Folder 29)
  - Item 12: Definition of Area of Production, Publication (Box 90, Folder 29)
  - Item 13: H.R. 13712, 1966; Publication (Box 90, Folder 29)
    Notes: May 27, 1966
  - Item 14: Defining and Delimiting the Term "Talent Fees", Publication (Box 90, Folder 29)
  - Item 15: S. 2475, Publication (Box 90, Folder 29)
  - Item 16: Public Law 89-601, 1966; Publication (Box 90, Folder 29)
    Notes: September 23, 1966
  - Item 17: Contract Mail Haulers, Publication (Box 90, Folder 29)
  - Item 18: S. 2475, Publication (Box 90, Folder 29)
  - Item 19: H.R. 5856, Publication (Box 90, Folder 29)
  - Item 20: Public Law 89-601, 1966; Publication (Box 90, Folder 29)
- Box: 90, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 90, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Exemptions Applicable to Agriculture, Processing of Agricultural Commodities, and Related Subjects, Publication (Box 90, Folder 30)
  - Item 2: Employment of Homeworkers in Certain Industries, Publication (Box 90, Folder 30)
  - Item 3: Equal Pay for Equal Work, Publication (Box 90, Folder 30)
  - Item 4: Equal Pay for Equal Work, Publication (Box 90, Folder 30)
  - Item 5: Employment of Learners, Publication (Box 90, Folder 30)
  - Item 6: Employment of Learners, Publication (Box 90, Folder 30)
  - Item 7: Exemption From Maximum Hours, 1964; Publication (Box 90, Folder 30)
    Notes: June 1964
  - Item 8: Exemption from Maximum Hours, 1963; Publication (Box 90, Folder 30)
    Notes: May 31, 1963
  - Item 9: Employment of Student-Learners, Publication (Box 90, Folder 30)
  - Item 10: Employment of Student-Learners, 1962; Publication (Box 90, Folder 30)
    Notes: March 31, 1962
  - Item 11: Employment of Handicapped Clients in Sheltered Workshops, Publication (Box 90, Folder 30)
  - Item 12: Employment of Messengers, 1964; Publication (Box 90, Folder 30)
  - Item 13: Employment of Messengers, 1963; Publication (Box 90, Folder 30)
  - Item 14: Employment of Messengers, 1965; Publication (Box 90, Folder 30)
    Notes: May 11, 1965
  - Item 15: Exemption of Certain Radio and Television Station Employees, Publication (Box 90, Folder 30)
  - Item 16: Exemptions of Certain Radio and Television Station Employees, 1965; Publication (Box 90, Folder 30)
    Notes: April 13, 1965
  - Item 17: Employment of Handicapped Person, Publication (Box 90, Folder 30)
  - Item 18: Employment of Handicapped Persons, 1965; Publication (Box 90, Folder 30)
    Notes: May 5, 1965
  - Item 19: Public Law 89-601, 1966; Publication (Box 90, Folder 30)
  - Item 20: Equal Pay for Equal Work, 1967; Publication (Box 90, Folder 30)
    Notes: April 14, 1967
  - Item 21: Employment of Full-Time Students, 1964; Publication (Box 90, Folder 30)
    Notes: December 7, 1964
  - Item 22: Employment of Full-Time Students in Retail or Service Establishments at Special Minimum Wages, 1966; Publication (Box 90, Folder 30)
    Notes: April 7, 1966
  - Item 23: Employment of Student Workers, 1966; Publication (Box 90, Folder 30)
  - Item 24: Employment of Handicapped Clients in Sheltered Workshops, 1965; Publication (Box 90, Folder 30)
    Notes: April 16, 1965
- Box: 90, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 90, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: General Statement, 1966; Publication (Box 90, Folder 31)
  - Item 2: General Statement, 1965; Publication (Box 90, Folder 31)
  - Item 3: The Fair Labor Standards Act as Applied to Retailers of Goods or Services, 1964; Publication (Box 90, Folder 31)
  - Item 4: The Fair Labor Standards Act as Applied to Retailers of Goods or Services, 1965; Publication (Box 90, Folder 31)
    Notes: June 10, 1965
  - Item 5: Forestry or Logging Operations in Which Not More Than Twelve Employees Are Employed, 1964; Publication (Box 90, Folder 31)
  - Item 6: The Fair Labor Standards Act as Applied to Establishments Engaged in Laundering, 1965; Publication (Box 90, Folder 31)
  - Item 7: The Fair Labor Standards Act as Applied to Establishments Engaged in Laundering, Cleaning or Repairing, 1964; Publication (Box 90, Folder 31)
  - Item 8: Forestry or Logging Operations in Which Not More Than Twelve Employees Are Employed, 1965; Publication (Box 90, Folder 31)
  - Item 9: General Safety and Health Standards for Federal Supply Contracts, 1966; Publication (Box 90, Folder 31)
  - Item 10: General Coverage of the Wage and Hours Provisions, 1966; Publication (Box 90, Folder 31)
  - Item 11: General Coverage of the Wage and Hours Provisions, 1964; Publication (Box 90, Folder 31)
    Notes: September 1964
  - Item 12: Fair Labor Standards Act, 1964; Publication (Box 90, Folder 31)
    Notes: January 1964
  - Item 13: Fair Labor Standards Amendments, 1966; Publication (Box 90, Folder 31)
    Notes: September 6, 1966
  - Item 14: Fair Labor Standards Amendments, 1966; Publication (Box 90, Folder 31)
    Notes: August 23, 1966
- Box: 90, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 90, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Handy Reference Guide to the Fair Labor Standards Act, 1966; Publication (Box 90, Folder 32)
    Notes: October 1966
  - Item 2: Highlights of the Fair Labo Standards Act, Publication (Box 90, Folder 32)
  - Item 3: How the Fair Labor Standards Act Applies to Automotive Parts Wholesaling, 1964; Publication (Box 90, Folder 32)
    Notes: October 1964
  - Item 4: Hired Farm Workers Under the Fair Labor Standards Act, 1966; Publication (Box 90, Folder 32)
  - Item 5: Laudries and Dry Cleaning Establishments, 1966; Publication (Box 90, Folder 32)
    Notes: November 1966
  - Item 6: Hospitals and Nursing Homes, 1966; Publication (Box 90, Folder 32)
  - Item 7: Bill to Amend Fair Labor Standards Act, 1961; Publication (Box 90, Folder 32)
    Notes: April 21, 1961
  - Item 8: Text of Fair Labor Standards Act, 1961; Publication (Box 90, Folder 32)
    Notes: May 12, 1961
  - Item 9: Handy Reference Guide to the Fair Labor Standards Act, 1966; Publication (Box 90, Folder 32)
  - Item 10: Hours Worked, 1966; Publication (Box 90, Folder 32)
    Notes: April 13, 1966
  - Item 11: Hours Worked, 1965; Publication (Box 90, Folder 32)
  - Item 12: Industries of a Seasonal Nature, 1965; Publication (Box 90, Folder 32)
    Notes: August 23, 1965
  - Item 13: Joint Employment Relationship, 1965; Publication (Box 90, Folder 32)
  - Item 14: Handy Reference Guide to the Fair Labor Standards Act, 1963; Publication (Box 90, Folder 32)
    Notes: April 1963
  - Item 15: Handy Reference Guide to the Fair Labor Standards Act, Publication (Box 90, Folder 32)
  - Item 16: Institutions of Higher Education, 1973; Publication (Box 90, Folder 32)
    Notes: April 1973
- Box: 90, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 90, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: New Wage-Hour Recordkeeping Regulations, Publication (Box 90, Folder 33)
    Author: Prentice-Hall
  - Item 2: New Record-Keeping Rules Under the Wage-Hour Law, Publication (Box 90, Folder 33)
  - Item 3: Provisions of the Fair Labor Standards Act, 1965; Publication (Box 90, Folder 33)
    Notes: April 29, 1965
  - Item 4: Overtime Compensation, 1966; Publication (Box 90, Folder 33)
    Notes: August 19, 1966
  - Item 5: Overtime Compensation, 1964; Publication (Box 90, Folder 33)
  - Item 6: Overtime Compensation, 1965; Publication (Box 90, Folder 33)
    Notes: April 1, 1965
- Box: 90, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 90, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Retail and Service Establishment and Related Exemptions, 1954; Publication (Box 90, Folder 34)
    Notes: April 1954
  - Item 2: Records to be Kept by Employers, Publication (Box 90, Folder 34)
  - Item 3: Radiation Safety and Health Standards for Federal Supply Contracts, Publication (Box 90, Folder 34)
  - Item 4: Records to be Kept by Employers, Publication (Box 90, Folder 34)
  - Item 5: Records to be Kept by Employers, Publication (Box 90, Folder 34)
  - Item 6: Records, Publication (Box 90, Folder 34)
  - Item 7: Records, 1964; Publication (Box 90, Folder 34)
  - Item 8: Services to the Public, 1966; Publication (Box 90, Folder 34)
    Notes: May 1966
  - Item 9: Wage Order Procedure for Puerto Rico, Publication (Box 90, Folder 34)
  - Item 10: Wage Order Procedure for Puerto Rico, Publication (Box 90, Folder 34)
- Box: 90, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 90, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Regulations, 1918; Publication (Box 90, Folder 35)
    Author: U.S. Employees' Compensation Commission
- Box: 90, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 90, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Public Law 89-488, 1966; Publication (Box 90, Folder 36)
    Notes: July 4, 1966
  - Item 2: Federal Employees' Compensation Act, 1966; Publication (Box 90, Folder 36)
    Notes: March 2, 1966
- Box: 90, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 90, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Federal Employees Health Benefits Act, 1966; Publication (Box 90, Folder 37)
  - Item 2: Additional Health Benefits Plans, 1966; Publication (Box 90, Folder 37)
    Notes: February 23, 1966
- Box: 90, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 90, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Public Law 89-329, 1965; Publication (Box 90, Folder 39)
    Notes: November 8, 1965
  - Item 2: Higher Education Act, Publication (Box 90, Folder 39)
    Author: U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare
- Box: 90, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 90, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations and the Taft-Hartley Law, Publication (Box 90, Folder 40)
  - Item 2: How the Taft-Hartley Bill Will Affect Your Employer-Employee Relations, 1947; Publication (Box 90, Folder 40)
    Author: National Foremen's Institute
  - Item 3: A Guide for Labor Organizations, 1948; Publication (Box 90, Folder 40)
    Author: National Labor Relations Board
  - Item 4: The AF of L Case for a Just Labor Law, Publication (Box 90, Folder 40)
    Author: American Federation of Labor
  - Item 5: The Wood Bill, Publication (Box 90, Folder 40)
  - Item 6: Has Taft-Hartley Act Served Public Interest?, Publication (Box 90, Folder 40)
    Author: Commonwealth Club of California
  - Item 7: The Taft-Hartley Labor Law, Publication (Box 90, Folder 40)
    Author: Research Institute of America
  - Item 8: Proposed Amendments to the Taft Hartley Law, 1953; Publication (Box 90, Folder 40)
    Author: New York Chamber of Commerce
    Notes: April 1953
  - Item 9: Declaration of Indignation, Publication (Box 90, Folder 40)
    Author: Foundation for Management Research
  - Item 10: This is Aimed at You!, Publication (Box 90, Folder 40)
    Author: New York Council of the International Association of Machinists
  - Item 11: Employee Rights Under the Taft-Hartley Act, 1947; Publication (Box 90, Folder 40)
    Author: National Electrical Manufacturers Association
    Notes: October 27, 1947
  - Item 12: Employee Rights, 1947; Publication (Box 90, Folder 40)
  - Item 13: Eligibility of Strikers to Vote, 1948; Publication (Box 90, Folder 40)
    Author: American Management Association
  - Item 14: Digest of Labor Management Act of 1947, Publication (Box 90, Folder 40)
  - Item 15: Are Attacks on the Taft-Hartley Law Justified?, Publication (Box 90, Folder 40)
  - Item 16: The Implications for Executives in the 1947 Labor-Management Relations Act, Publication (Box 90, Folder 40)
    Author: The Budd Company
  - Item 17: The Impact of the New Labor Law on Union-Management Relations, 1948; Publication (Box 90, Folder 40)
    Author: Leo Cyril Brown
  - Item 18: Bibliography, Publication (Box 90, Folder 40)
  - Item 19: Selected Bibliography of the Labor Management Relations Act, 1950; Publication (Box 90, Folder 40)
    Notes: November 1950
- Box: 91, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Issues in Labor-Management Relations, Publication (Box 91, Folder 1)
    Author: John Shott
  - Item 2: A Guide for Labor Organizations to the Filing Requirements, 1952; Publication (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: What Should the Businessman Know About the Taft-Hartley Act, Publication (Box 91, Folder 1)
    Author: Thomas J. McDermott
  - Item 4: The Problem of Delay in Administering the Labor-Management Relations Act, 1952; Publication (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Labor Law in the Public Interest, 1953; Publication (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Taft Hartley Prospecst, Publication (Box 91, Folder 1)
    Author: Public Affairs Institute
  - Item 7: Labor-Management Relations Act, 1947; Publication (Box 91, Folder 1)
    Notes: June 3, 1947
  - Item 8: The Labor-Management Relations Act, Publication (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: The Labor-Management Relations Act, Publication (Box 91, Folder 1)
    Author: Mill & Factory
  - Item 10: Labor-Management Relations Act, 1954; Publication (Box 91, Folder 1)
    Notes: April 15, 1954
  - Item 11: Public Law 101, Publication (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Labor-Management Relations Act, 1947; Publication (Box 91, Folder 1)
    Notes: June 30, 1947
  - Item 13: The Labor-Management Relations Act, 1947; Publication (Box 91, Folder 1)
    Author: Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America
    Notes: June 28, 1947
  - Item 14: Labor Management Relations Act, Publication (Box 91, Folder 1)
    Author: Library of Congress
  - Item 15: Ives, 1957; Publication (Box 91, Folder 1)
    Author: Ives
    Notes: November 21, 1957
- Box: 91, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Taft-Hartley Law and its Successor, 1949; Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
    Notes: February 1949
  - Item 2: Revision of the Taft-Hartley Act, 1948; Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
    Author: Editorial Research Reports
    Notes: December 1, 1948
  - Item 3: The Supervisor's Guide to the Taft-Hartley Act, Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: That New Labor Law, Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Taft-Hartley Information Pamphlet for Employees, Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: The Truth about the Labor-Management Relations Act, Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
    Author: Republican National Committee
  - Item 7: The Taft-Hartley Act in Operation, Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
    Author: Max Malin, S. Herbert Unterberger
  - Item 8: The Taft-Hartley Act, 1948; Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
    Author: Social Action Magazine
    Notes: April 15, 1948
  - Item 9: The Public and the Taft-Hartley Law, Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Political Maneuvering Kill Chances for Amending Taft-Hartley Labor Law, 1954; Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
    Author: Yale University
    Notes: May 30, 1954
  - Item 11: Present Status of Labor-Management Relations Act, 1953; Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
    Notes: April 22, 1953
  - Item 12: Will the Taft-Hartley Law Bring Industrial Peace?, 1947; Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
    Author: Queens College Radio Forum
    Notes: November 20, 1947
  - Item 13: Remarks Before the Minnesota Employers' Association, 1948; Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
    Notes: January 30, 1948
- Box: 91, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Reports Required Under the LMRDA, Publication (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Reporting and Bonding Provisions, 1967; Publication (Box 91, Folder 3)
    Notes: March 1967
  - Item 3: How the Law Affects Unions, Publication (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Rights and Responsibilities Under the LMRDA, Publication (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Union Safeguards, Publication (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: What is Required Under the Law, Publication (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Reports Required from Union Officials and Employees, Publication (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Employer and Consultant Reporting, Publication (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: The Landrum-Griffin Act, 1962; Publication (Box 91, Folder 3)
    Author: John L. Holcombe
    Notes: February 1962
- Box: 91, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act, 1959; Publication (Box 91, Folder 4)
    Notes: September 10, 1959
  - Item 2: Understanding the 1959 Labor Law, Publication (Box 91, Folder 4)
    Author: Joseph E. Finley
  - Item 3: Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act, 1959; Publication (Box 91, Folder 4)
    Notes: September 3, 1959
  - Item 4: Section by Section Analysis, 1959; Publication (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: New Labor Law of 1959, Publication (Box 91, Folder 4)
    Author: Commerce Clearing House
  - Item 6: National Labor Relations Act, Publication (Box 91, Folder 4)
    Author: U.S. National Labor Relations Board
  - Item 7: The 1959 Labor Reform Law, Publication (Box 91, Folder 4)
    Author: American Retail Federation
  - Item 8: Labor Organization Financial Reporting, 1959; Publication (Box 91, Folder 4)
    Notes: September 14, 1959
  - Item 9: Comment on Labor-Management and Disclosure Act, 1960; Publication (Box 91, Folder 4)
    Author: American Civil Liberties Union
    Notes: March 25, 1960
  - Item 10: Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act, 1959; Publication (Box 91, Folder 4)
    Notes: September 1959
- Box: 91, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Regulations, 1965; Publication (Box 91, Folder 5)
    Notes: November 1965
- Box: 91, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: MDTA Training Program, 1964; Publication (Box 91, Folder 6)
    Notes: December 1964
  - Item 2: Trade Unions, Publication (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Public Law 87-415, 1962; Publication (Box 91, Folder 6)
    Notes: March 15, 1962
  - Item 4: Public Law 89-15, 1965; Publication (Box 91, Folder 6)
    Notes: April 26, 1965
  - Item 5: Public Law 89-792, 1966; Publication (Box 91, Folder 6)
    Notes: November 7, 1966
  - Item 6: Manpower Act of 1965, Publication (Box 91, Folder 6)
    Notes: April 12, 1965
  - Item 7: Manpower Development and Training Act, Publication (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Manpower Development and Training Act, 1962; Publication (Box 91, Folder 6)
    Notes: March 12, 1962
  - Item 9: Manpower Development and Training Amendments, 1966; Publication (Box 91, Folder 6)
    Notes: September 8, 1966
  - Item 10: Looking for Skilled Workers, Publication (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: The Manpower Development and Training Act, Publication (Box 91, Folder 6)
    Notes: The Manpower Development and Training Act
  - Item 12: MDTA, Publication (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: Training Activities Under the Manpower Development and Training Act, Publication (Box 91, Folder 6)
- Box: 91, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The National Defense Student Loan Program, Publication (Box 91, Folder 7)
- Box: 91, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: National Labor Relations Act, 1935; Publication (Box 91, Folder 8)
    Author: American Liberty League
    Notes: September 5, 1935
- Box: 91, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Stop Congress from Cutting Wages, Publication (Box 91, Folder 9)
    Author: Labor's Non-Partisan League
  - Item 2: To the Librarian, 1939; Publication (Box 91, Folder 9)
    Notes: March 13, 1939
  - Item 3: The Wagner Act, Publication (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: National Labor Relations Board, Publication (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: A Layman's Guide to Basic Law, 1971; Publication (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: A Layman's Guide to Basic Law, 1964; Publication (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: A Layman's Guide to Basic Law, 1971; Publication (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: A Layman's Guide to Basic Law, Publication (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: A Layman's Guide to Basic Law, 1970; Publication (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Item 10: Protect the National Labor Relations Act, Publication (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Item 11: The National Labor Relations Act, 1962; Publication (Box 91, Folder 9)
    Author: University of Minnesota
    Notes: March 1962
  - Item 12: Older Americans Community Service Program, 1966; Publication (Box 91, Folder 9)
    Notes: October 13, 1966
- Box: 91, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Walsh-Healey Act, Publication (Box 91, Folder 10)
- Box: 91, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 91, Folder 11)